Guide to the John Holmstrom Papers and Punk Magazine Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Writings and correspondence, Series II
  - Notecards in Holmstrom's hand, labels from a private showing of materials from the Punk Magazine archive in 2012. (Box 56)
  - John Holmstrom & Batton Lash. "IT Lurks Within!". Items related to Holmstrom's high school years., circa 1968-1971 (Box 56)
  - Reviews from one or more "Punk Listening Parties" with reviews by Legs McNeil, John Holmstrom, Avi Spivak and others., circa 2002-2004 (Box 56)
  - "Punk Magazine Awards Ballot" completed signed illegibly ("Ira Kohls?") with "Mick Jones" written underneath., 1979 (Box 56)
  - Mary Harron. "Johnny Rotten", transcript of an interview with Johnny Rotten., 1976 (Box 56)
  - Susan Springfield. "Give Me Hell." Photocopied review of a performance by Richard Hell and the Voidoids at the Village Gate., 1977 (Box 56)
  - John Holmstrom. "John Holmstrom and Eldridge Cleaver.", circa 1980s (Box 56)
  - A., Dale, undated (Box 54)
  - Abrams, Leonard, 1983 (Box 54)
  - Agi, Yuzahu, undated (Box 54)
  - Apgar, Susanna, 2002 (Box 54)
  - Albanese, N, 1986 (Box 54)
  - Alfonso, Ralph, 1976-1982 (Box 54)
  - Allen, Claudia, 1999 (Box 54)
  - Allweiss, D, 1974 (Box 54)
  - American Entertainment Management, 1977 (Box 54)
  - Amuse New York, 1987 (Box 54)
  - Anderson, Lindsey, 2007 (Box 54)
  - Anne, ?, undated (Box 54)
  - Annie, ?, 1979 (Box 54)
  - Apocalyptic Productions, 1976 (Box 54)
  - Avidor, Ken, 1995-2003 (Box 54)
  - Backwards, Ace, 1983-2002 (Box 54)
  - Bagge, Peter and Joanne, 1983-1989 (Box 54)
  - Baker, Judith, 2003 (Box 54)
  - Balfour, Brad, undated (Box 54)
  - Balm, Trixie A, 1976 (Box 54)
  - Balogh, D, 1980 (Box 54)
  - Bar, ?, undated (Box 54)
  - Barbara Ann Levy Gallery, 2001 (Box 54)
  - Barrett, Charles, 1976 (Box 54)
  - Bartlett, G, 1977 (Box 54)
  - Baruth, John, 1976 (Box 54)
  - Bat, ?, undated (Box 54)
  - Bayley, Roberta, 1976-1980 (Box 54)
  - Beauchamp, Monte S, 1987-2004 (Box 54)
  - Bedard, Stacey, 1988 (Box 54)
  - Benson, Robin, 1977 (Box 54)
  - Berhowitz, Barak, 1976 (Box 54)
  - Bernstein, A.D, 1983 (Box 54)
  - Bernstein, Anne, 1982 (Box 54)
  - Bernstein, Helene, 1976 (Box 54)
  - Berry, Annette, 1989 (Box 54)
  - Bidewell, Joe; includes photographs, 1977 (Box 54)
  - Big Bad Dodgy, 2000 (Box 54)
  - Binder, Ronald, 1979-2003 (Box 54)
  - Biniek, George, 1993 (Box 54)
  - Bisbort, Alan L, undated (Box 54)
  - Blackstock, Ray, 1990 (Box 54)
  - Bockris, Victor, 1978-1996 (Box 54)
  - Boston Graphic News, 1976 (Box 54)
  - Boteler, Marilyn, 1979 (Box 54)
  - Boutillier, Helena, 2003 (Box 54)
  - Boyar, Esq., Andrew, 1996 (Box 54)
  - [Burroughs, William S.], James Grauerholz, Secretary, 1976-1977 (Box 54)
  - Bromberg, M, 1977 (Box 54)
  - Brooklyn Museum, 1974 (Box 54)
  - Brotman, Dan, 1989 (Box 54)
  - Brown, Michael Martin, 1976 (Box 54)
  - Burd, David, 2001 (Box 54)
  - Burke, Susan, undated (Box 54)
  - Burkhart, Fred, undated (Box 54)
  - [Clingensmith, Evelyn], Fatso, 1976 (Box 54)
  - Cadillac Castle Gallery, 2007 (Box 54)
  - Camilla, ?, undated (Box 54)
  - Candace Perich Gallery, 1996 (Box 54)
  - Capital City Distribution, 1984 (Box 54)
  - Carleton, Bruce, circa 1984 (Box 54)
  - Carpenter, Lee D, 1974 (Box 54)
  - Cartoon, 1975 (Box 54)
  - Cartoonists Co-Op Press, 1974 (Box 54)
  - Cary, 1999 (Box 54)
  - Casey, S, 1978 (Box 54)
  - Cedeno, Alex, 1989 (Box 54)
  - Champouer, Laurence, undated (Box 54)
  - Charlotte, 2003 (Box 54)
  - Chepra, 1992 (Box 54)
  - Chip, undated (Box 54)
  - Chris and Greg, undated (Box 54)
  - Christiano, Mary Anne, undated (Box 54)
  - Chrysalis Records, 1979 (Box 54)
  - Cisa, undated (Box 54)
  - Cleaver, Eldridge, 1985-1986 (Box 54)
  - co-Workers, undated (Box 54)
  - Cohen, Miriam, Summer, 1975 (Box 54)
  - Cohen, Susan Lee, 2004 (Box 54)
  - Coleson, David, 1986 (Box 54)
  - Collins, Arthur, undated (Box 54)
  - Cory, 1986 (Box 54)
  - Cosmo, undated, 2001 (Box 54)
  - Costas, Laura, 1974-1988 (Box 54)
  - Coulson, Bud Bennett, 2000 (Box 54)
  - Coulson, David, undated, 2001 (Box 54)
  - Court of Probate, 1993 (Box 54)
  - Cowen, 1994 (Box 54)
  - Cox, Heather, 1987 (Box 54)
  - Crawford, John, 1983 (Box 54)
  - Criuckshank, Dale, 1987 (Box 54)
  - Crumb, R., artwork included., 1976, 1983 (Box 54)
  - Cruse, Howard, 1986 (Box 54)
  - Cummings, John, undated (Box 54)
  - D. P. Board, 1983 (Box 54)
  - Dadomo, 1977 (Box 54)
  - Dale, 1981-1986 (Box 54)
  - Daniel Wolf, Inc, 1992 (Box 54)
  - Darland, Terry, 1991 (Box 54)
  - Davello, J, 1976 (Box 54)
  - Davis, Ryan, 1980 (Box 54)
  - Dawson, Diane, circa 1976 (Box 54)
  - Deborah, 1983-1984 (Box 54)
  - Deer Gallery, 1993 (Box 54)
  - Denney, Alice, 1978 (Box 54)
  - Diana's, 1981 (Box 54)
  - DJK Productions, 2005 (Box 54)
  - Dominick, Guy, 1984 (Box 54)
  - Dougherty, Paul, 1993-2003 (Box 54)
  - Downey, Lynn, 1990 (Box 54)
  - Drazan, Dale, 1997 (Box 54)
  - Driller, Mel, 1976 (Box 54)
  - Drus, 1978 (Box 54)
  - Dubisch, Michael, undated (Box 54)
  - Dudley, Gordon, 2006 (Box 54)
  - Duncan, B. N, 1987 (Box 54)
  - Dunn, Jr, 1975-1976 (Box 54)
  - Eagen, Pamela, 1977 (Box 54)
  - Edison, Los, undated (Box 54)
  - Edsall, Anne, 1984 (Box 54)
  - Ehmann, Aby, 2004 (Box 54)
  - Eichmann, William Mrs, 1973 (Box 54)
  - Eileen, undated (Box 54)
  - Eisner, Will, 1974 (Box 54)
  - Ellis, James, undated (Box 54)
  - Engh, Leslie, 2007 (Box 54)
  - Entrekin, Morgan, 1983 (Box 54)
  - Ernst, 1993 (Box 54)
  - Esther, 1988 (Box 54)
  - Expidi Printing, 1984-1994 (Box 54)
  - Field, Gil, undated (Box 54)
  - Field, Larry, 1979 (Box 54)
  - Finlator, 1991 (Box 54)
  - Fiorilla, S, 1988 (Box 54)
  - Firmin, 1980 (Box 54)
  - Fisher, Jason, 1988 (Box 54)
  - Fishwrap, 2000 (Box 54)
  - Fjorkenstad, Sandra, undated (Box 54)
  - Flippo, Chet, 1980 (Box 54)
  - Flowers, Eddie, 1976-1977 (Box 54)
  - Flynn, Mike, 2007 (Box 54)
  - Forcade, Tom, 1989 (Box 54)
  - Francisco, Michelle, 2004 (Box 54)
  - Fricke, Bill, 1993 (Box 54)
  - Fridee, David, undated (Box 54)
  - Gale, Janet, undated (Box 54)
  - Gardner, Thom, undated (Box 54)
  - Geerdes, Clay, undated (Box 54)
  - Gelin, Ed, 1983 (Box 54)
  - Gendron, Bernard, 2001 (Box 54)
  - Gene, undated (Box 54)
  - Geneval, 1998 (Box 54)
  - Gilibert, Chouket, 1977 (Box 54)
  - Givad, Drag, undated (Box 54)
  - Godlis, David, 1980-1999 (Box 54)
  - Goldstein, Al, undates (Box 54)
  - Goodson, L.B, 1989 (Box 54)
  - Gradia, Wade & Cary, 1997-2005 (Box 54)
  - Grand Slam, undated (Box 54)
  - Grayson, Gary, 1994 (Box 54)
  - Griffith, Bill, undated (Box 54)
  - Grimmer, D.P., 1992 (Box 54)
  - Grossman, Bobby, 1978 (Box 54)
  - Gruen, Bob and Elizabeth, 1995-2008 (Box 54)
  - Guterman, Jimmy, 1989 (Box 54)
  - Gypsy, undated (Box 54)
  - Hall, Mary Ann, 1976 (Box 54)
  - Hample, Stu, 1976 (Box 54)
  - Hargett, Dave, undated (Box 54)
  - Harron, Mary, circa 1976 (Box 54)
  - Harry, Deborah, 1977, 1983 (Box 54)
  - Haugh, Elizabeth & Bob, 1974-1982 (Box 54)
  - Haugh, J, 2001 (Box 54)
  - Haugh, Shelah, 1997 (Box 54)
  - Heavy Metal Magazine, 1981 (Box 54)
  - Heins, Derek, 1988 (Box 54)
  - Hektoen, 1979 (Box 54)
  - Helen Wheels Band, undated (Box 54)
  - Hellman, Danny, circa 1999 (Box 54)
  - Hellmuth, Stephen M, 1979 (Box 54)
  - High Times, circa 1990s (Box 54)
  - Hillberg, Lee & Haw, circa 1995 (Box 54)
  - Hines, Caitlyn, 1978 (Box 54)
  - Holmstrom, Frances J, 1976-1990 (Box 54)
  - Holmstrom, John, 1970-1999 (Box 54)
  - Holmstrom, Liz, 1993 (Box 54)
  - Honky Tonk Magazine, 1981 (Box 54)
  - Horn, Ike, 1976 (Box 54)
  - Hounds, The, undated (Box 54)
  - Howell, M, 1976 (Box 54)
  - Hughley, D, 1983 (Box 54)
  - Hurden, E, 1988 (Box 54)
  - Hutton, Lindsay, undated (Box 54)
  - ig (eyegee), undated (Box 54)
  - IDC Kids, 1977 (Box 54)
  - Independent Publications, 1983 (Box 54)
  - Independent Record Store, 1983 (Box 54)
  - Inge, 1977 (Box 54)
  - Inpress, Inc; includes photographs, undated (Box 54)
  - Isabella, Anne Marie, 1984 (Box 54)
  - Ivey, Todd, 2001-2007 (Box 54)
  - Jade, 1978 (Box 54)
  - Jeana, 1974 (Box 54)
  - Jenkins, Sandra, 1984 (Box 54)
  - Jim's Records, 1982-1983 (Box 54)
  - JK, 2001 (Box 54)
  - Johnson, 1991 (Box 54)
  - Johnstone, Kelly, 1988 (Box 54)
  - Jourdan, 1995 (Box 54)
  - Judy and Ralph, undated (Box 54)
  - Judy, 1990 (Box 54)
  - June, undated (Box 54)
  - Kahn - Braunstein, Leslie, 1977 (Box 54)
  - Kane, Patti, undated (Box 54)
  - Katz, Tom, 1978 (Box 54)
  - Kawano, Jon, 1976 (Box 54)
  - Kearns, Burt, undated (Box 54)
  - Keeps, Dave, undated (Box 54)
  - Kennedy, Jay, 1981 (Box 54)
  - Kennedy, Michael John, 1997-1999 (Box 54)
  - Kenny, Sarah, undated (Box 54)
  - Keogh, Bradley, 1989 (Box 54)
  - Kersig, Janelle, 1998 (Box 54)
  - Kevin, undated (Box 54)
  - Kim and Roberta, undated (Box 54)
  - King, J.D, 1997 (Box 54)
  - King, Paul, 1987 (Box 54)
  - Kircher, Paul, 1976 (Box 54)
  - Kitchen Sink Press, 1997 (Box 54)
  - Kitchen, Denis, 1988 (Box 54)
  - Kitchen, Jim, 1988 (Box 54)
  - KK, 2005 (Box 54)
  - Knapp, Kevin, 1977 (Box 54)
  - Koenig, John M, undated (Box 54)
  - Kohnowich, Susan, 1976-2005 (Box 54)
  - Kolstein, Janet, 1977 (Box 54)
  - Kominsky, Aline, 1974 (Box 54)
  - Koopersmith, Adrienne Sioux, 1994 (Box 54)
  - Koshonski, 1977 (Box 54)
  - Kramer, Jacob, 1996 (Box 54)
  - Krupp Comic Works, Inc, 1976 (Box 54)
  - Kuhrman, Paul, 1974-2002 (Box 54)
  - Kurtzman, Harvey, 1974-1992 (Box 54)
  - La Pilusa, Judy, 1976-1977 (Box 54)
  - Lagger, Ken, 1974-1975 (Box 54)
  - Lago, Ian C, 1996 (Box 54)
  - Langsam, Ida, 1995 (Box 54)
  - Larson, F, 1984 (Box 54)
  - Lash, Amy, 1996 (Box 54)
  - Lash, Batton A., 1973 (Box 54)
  - Leahe, Dale, 1984 (Box 54)
  - Leogrande, Ernest, circa 1976 (Box 54)
  - Leone, Barbara, 1997 (Box 54)
  - Lesher, Charlotte, 2004-2006 (Box 54)
  - Levitt, 1977 (Box 54)
  - Levitt, Shelley, 1977 (Box 54)
  - Levy, Michelle, 1974 (Box 54)
  - Lina, undated (Box 54)
  - Linna, Miriam, undated (Box 54)
  - Little Italy, 1980 (Box 54)
  - Lopatin, 1976 (Box 54)
  - Lopez, Dennis, 1976-1978 (Box 54)
  - Lorenzea, Jan, undated (Box 54)
  - Louch, F, 1983 (Box 54)
  - Lufers, Chief, undated (Box 54)
  - Lynch, Jay, undated (Box 54)
  - Lynne, 1989 (Box 54)
  - Lyons, Jude, 1985 (Box 54)
  - [MacSpade], Aido, circa 1986 (Box 54)
  - Mace, Lenny, undated (Box 54)
  - Madison Square Press, 1985 (Box 54)
  - Mambo Club Studios, 1978 (Box 54)
  - Manic Panic, 1977 (Box 54)
  - Manitoba & Jershurin, undated (Box 54)
  - Manley, Colleen C, 1989 (Box 54)
  - Manoeuvre, Phillippe, 1978 (Box 54)
  - Manor, Stanley Wayne, undated (Box 54)
  - Margaret Anne, 1977 (Box 54)
  - Marina, undated (Box 54)
  - Marshall, Randall, 1975 (Box 54)
  - Martin, Peggy A, 1976 (Box 54)
  - Massey, Edie, 1978 (Box 54)
  - Mastrianni, Tony, 1976 (Box 54)
  - Matlock, Mandie, 1988 (Box 54)
  - Mavrides, 1990 (Box 54)
  - Max's Kansas City Project, 2005 (Box 54)
  - McBurnie, K, 1983 (Box 54)
  - McCabe, Barbara, 2002 (Box 54)
  - McCandless, Ann, 1976 (Box 54)
  - McDowell, Gail, 1977 (Box 54)
  - McGough, David, 1977 (Box 54)
  - McGuire, Judy, 1992 (Box 54)
  - McNeil, Legs, circa 2000 (Box 54)
  - McNichol, Carol, 1976 (Box 54)
  - Merrill, Dand, 1984 (Box 54)
  - Michael, 1991 (Box 54)
  - Michigan Police Department, 1997 (Box 54)
  - Mickey, 2005 (Box 54)
  - Milkshake Man, 1983-1993 (Box 54)
  - Miller, E., 1984 (Box 54)
  - Miller, Marc and Bette Ringma, 1979 (Box 54)
  - Miller, S, 1977 (Box 54)
  - Mills, A, 1977 (Box 54)
  - Miura, Setsu, 1978 (Box 54)
  - Mongon, Paolo, 2001 (Box 54)
  - Moore, Carol, 1990-1991 (Box 54)
  - Morelos, Michelle, 2005 (Box 54)
  - Morgan, Jeffrey, undated (Box 54)
  - Mosher, Stephanie, 2003 (Box 54)
  - Most, Mary, 1977-1979 (Box 54)
  - Motels, The, undated (Box 54)
  - Mott, 1999 (Box 54)
  - Niagara, 1977-2004 (Box 55)
  - Nickelodeon, undated (Box 55)
  - Olsen, Carl, 1992 (Box 55)
  - Ornsteen, Cindy, 1988 (Box 55)
  - OSB, 2003 (Box 55)
  - Otis, Jeffrey F, 1993 (Box 55)
  - Ozone, undated (Box 55)
  - P., Fran, 1976 (Box 55)
  - Pan and Peter, 1983 (Box 55)
  - Parachute Press, Inc, 1983-1988 (Box 55)
  - Parfitt, 1991 (Box 55)
  - Parks, Bruce, undated (Box 55)
  - Parson's The New School, 2006 (Box 55)
  - Pata, Sara, 1977 (Box 55)
  - Paul, Steve, 1976 (Box 55)
  - Peisch, Jeffrey, 1995 (Box 55)
  - Pellegrino, Sue, 1977 (Box 55)
  - Pelzmen, Franny, 1977 (Box 55)
  - Pentagon Papers, Inc, 1983 (Box 55)
  - Pepe, Barbara, 1976 (Box 55)
  - Perlov, 1976 (Box 55)
  - Peter and Joanne, undated (Box 55)
  - Peter, undated (Box 55)
  - Peters, Tommy, 1980 (Box 55)
  - Phantom, 1983 (Box 55)
  - Phillips, Anye, circa 1978 (Box 55)
  - Phreddie, Phast, circa 1976 (Box 55)
  - Piersanti, Robert, 2001 (Box 55)
  - Pippi, 1976 (Box 55)
  - Playboy, 1977 (Box 55)
  - Plympton, Bill, 1986 (Box 55)
  - Poe, Amos, undated (Box 55)
  - Polk, Eileen, 2005 (Box 55)
  - Porter, Trace, 1983 (Box 55)
  - Pousner, 1977 (Box 55)
  - Pozgay, Curt, undated (Box 55)
  - Pressler and Pressler, LLP, 2011 (Box 55)
  - Prevost, Gary, 1990 (Box 55)
  - Pria, Els, 1975 (Box 55)
  - Prine, Curtis, 1989 (Box 55)
  - Proposition, The, 2003 (Box 55)
  - Psychedelic Solution, 1986 (Box 55)
  - Psycho, 2006-2007 (Box 55)
  - Psychotronic, 1996 (Box 55)
  - Punk Magazine and John Holmstrom, undated (Box 55)
  - Ragan, "Sugarfoot", undated (Box 55)
  - Ragan, Patricia, 1978 (Box 55)
  - Ramone, 1985 (Box 55)
  - Ramone, Charlotte and Mickey, 2001 (Box 55)
  - Ramone, Joey, circa 1977 (Box 55)
  - Ramone, Johnny, 2000 (Box 55)
  - Ramones Comic Signing, 2005 (Box 55)
  - Ramones Fan Club, 1977 (Box 55)
  - Randy, Kent, 1981 (Box 55)
  - Rannelli, Wayne, 2005 (Box 55)
  - Rashtchian, 1987 (Box 55)
  - Reachout International, undated (Box 55)
  - Rebel Rouser Records, undated (Box 55)
  - The Record Junkie, 1978 (Box 55)
  - Recordvision, 1983 (Box 55)
  - Reet, El, 1982 (Box 55)
  - Regan, Patricia, 1973 (Box 55)
  - Reinert, Rick, 1987 (Box 55)
  - Reininger, Gustave, 1983 (Box 55)
  - Rettmer, Denise, 1986-1991 (Box 55)
  - Ribicoff, Sarai, 1977 (Box 55)
  - Richard, Normon, undated (Box 55)
  - Richardson, Regina, undated (Box 55)
  - Ricks, Dave, undated (Box 55)
  - Rieben, Rolf, 1985 (Box 55)
  - Rob and Bonnie, 1998 (Box 55)
  - Robertson, Rob, 1980 (Box 55)
  - Robin, I'ma, 1976 (Box 55)
  - Robinson, Lisa, 1976 (Box 55)
  - Rock and Roll Hall of Fame, 1993-1998 (Box 55)
  - Rockaway Records, 2004 (Box 55)
  - Rockpile Records, undated (Box 55)
  - Romagnoli, Robert, circa 1970s (Box 55)
  - Rose, Cynthia, 1977-1985 (Box 55)
  - Rose, Mickey; also contains zines, undated (Box 55)
  - Rosenbaum, Ron, undated (Box 55)
  - Rotolo, Carla, 1971 (Box 55)
  - Rowland, Bob, 1984 (Box 55)
  - Ruperts Goldsworth Gallery, 1998 (Box 55)
  - Sabino, Samuel, 1987 (Box 55)
  - Salisbury, 1971 (Box 55)
  - Sally and J.D, 1994 (Box 55)
  - Snyder, Chris, undated (Box 55)
  - Stromby, Nicole, undated (Box 55)
  - Salzer, Scruffs, undated (Box 55)
  - Sanctuary Publishing, 2003 (Box 55)
  - Saunders, Metal Mike, 1977 (Box 55)
  - Sawbuck, "Uncle", 1977 (Box 55)
  - Sblendorio, Lenny, undated (Box 55)
  - Scalper, Sara, 2014 (Box 55)
  - Schick, Lawrencem, 1983 (Box 55)
  - School of Visual Arts Alumni Society, 1987 (Box 55)
  - School of Visual Arts, 1982 (Box 55)
  - Sculatti, Gene, undated (Box 55)
  - Scurvy, Chris, 1986 (Box 55)
  - Shaw, Greg, 1976 (Box 55)
  - Shea, Jay, 1974 (Box 55)
  - Shell, Larry, 1984 (Box 55)
  - Sherman, B, 1980 (Box 55)
  - Shernoff, Andy, undated (Box 55)
  - Shirley, John, undated (Box 55)
  - Shultz, Thomas, 1992 (Box 55)
  - Simon and Gill, 1974 (Box 55)
  - Simpson, Don, undated (Box 55)
  - Singer, Robert, 1978 (Box 55)
  - Sire Records, 1979 (Box 55)
  - Snowbud, 1995 (Box 55)
  - So What, 1983 (Box 55)
  - Society of Illustrators, 1986-1992 (Box 55)
  - Spa and Powerhouse Books, undated (Box 55)
  - Sparkis, Joseph, 2007 (Box 55)
  - Spence, 1989 (Box 55)
  - Sperrazza, Gary, circa 1983 (Box 55)
  - Springer, Cole, circa 1976 (Box 55)
  - St. Clair, Caroline, undated (Box 55)
  - Stathis, Lou, 1977-1984 (Box 55)
  - Stein, Chris, circa 1978 (Box 55)
  - Steinberg, Flo, 1976 (Box 55)
  - Sterling, Robert, 2001 (Box 55)
  - Stine, Jane, 1984 (Box 55)
  - Strachan, John R, 1976 (Box 55)
  - Strahl, Audrey, 1979 (Box 55)
  - Streets, 1981 (Box 55)
  - Streets, Dee Dee, 1981 (Box 55)
  - Sue, undated (Box 55)
  - Supina, Bob, 1981 (Box 55)
  - Suze, 1976 (Box 55)
  - T., Mike, 1994 (Box 55)
  - Tabak, Morton, 1996 (Box 55)
  - Taglianini, undated (Box 55)
  - Takahashi, Fusako, undated (Box 55)
  - Tandero, Erik, 2006 (Box 55)
  - Tarashir, Claudia, 1974 (Box 55)
  - Texas Department of Criminal Justice, 2010 (Box 55)
  - The Fast, undated (Box 55)
  - Tina, undated (Box 55)
  - Torn, Tony, circa 1979 (Box 55)
  - Traxler, Lisa, undated (Box 55)
  - Trese, Michael, 1976-1984 (Box 55)
  - Triestman, Greg, 1979 (Box 55)
  - Triggs, Teal, 2000 (Box 55)
  - Trimm, Jim, 1976 (Box 55)
  - Upstart Distribution, undated (Box 55)
  - United States Department of Education, 1984 (Box 55)
  - University of Wisconsin-Madison, 1981 (Box 55)
  - Valerie, 1976 (Box 55)
  - Vance, Kathy, 1991 (Box 55)
  - Venezia, H., 1976 (Box 55)
  - Vialet, Laurent, 2002 (Box 55)
  - Victor, 2010 (Box 55)
  - Viglione, Joseph Allen, 1976 (Box 55)
  - Wacaco, Frank, undated (Box 55)
  - Walsh, Peter, 2001 (Box 55)
  - Ward, Rich, 1987 (Box 55)
  - Watkins, Tom, 1978 (Box 55)
  - Webster, Jim, 1979 (Box 55)
  - Weiner, 1986-1989 (Box 55)
  - Weiners, undated (Box 55)
  - West, Mae, 1972 (Box 55)
  - Wetton, Nicholas, 1991 (Box 55)
  - Whizzograms, 1992 (Box 55)
  - Wiles, 1976 (Box 55)
  - Willemse, Richard, undated (Box 55)
  - Williams, J. R, 1996 (Box 55)
  - Williamson, 1973 (Box 55)
  - Winslow, Mitzi, undated (Box 55)
  - Wright, Patti, 1976 (Box 55)
  - Yonts, Chris and Cathy, 1999-2010 (Box 55)
  - Yoruba, 1976 (Box 55)
  - Yusk, Bill, 1984 (Box 55)
  - Z., Kathy, undated (Box 55)
  - Zack Company, Inc, 2002 (Box 55)
  - Zane, Emily, 1977 (Box 55)
  - Zed Records, 1981 (Box 55)
  - Zee, Ohne, undated (Box 55)
  - Ziesing Bros, 1983 (Box 55)
  - Ziesing, Mark, 1982 (Box 55)
  - Zone, Miki, 1976 (Box 55)
  - Zoologique, Jardin, 1981 (Box 55)
  - From Eddie Flowers to John Holmstrom., 1976 (Box 56)
  - From Greg Shaw to John Holmstrom., 1976 (Box 56)
  - "Punk of the Month" submission for Monto Mania ("No!! This is not Dick Manitoba")., undated (Box 56)
- Business records, Series III
  - Punk business records (Box 57)
  - High Times business records (Box 59)
  - High Times business records (Box 60)
  - Punk business ledgers (Box 61 (Oversize))
  - Holmstrom appointment books (Box 62)
  - Punk business records (Box 58)
- Photographs, Series IV
  - Photographs, mostly for Punk, 1970s-2000s (Box 63)
  - Photographs, mostly for Punk, 1970-1990's (Box 64 (Oversize))
- Printed materials, Series V
  - Printed proofs and pay copies of Punk and other publications, 1970s (Box 65)
  - Newspapers and magazines, 1990s-2000s (Box 66)
  - Newspapers and magazines, 1990s-2000s (Box 67)
  - Issues of The Spark and other publications, 1970s-2000s (Box 68 (Oversize))
  - Calendars, catalogs, and newspapers, 2000s (Box 69 (Oversize))
- Merchandise, Series VI
  - T-shirts, circa 2000s (Box 70)
  - T-shirts, circa 2000s (Box 71)
  - T-shirts, circa 2000s (Box 73)
  - T-shirts and sweatshirts, circa 2000s (Box 74)
  - T-shirts and wool hats, circa 2000s (Box 75)
  - T-shirts, sweater, circa 2000s (Box 76)
  - T-shirts, shirts and sweaters, circa 2000s (Box 77)
  - T-shirts, jacket, circa 2000s (Box 81)
  - Mug with wool hat, stickers, key chains, four baseball hats, buttons, two energy drink cans, circa 2000s (Box 79)
  - Punk bag, two purses, belts, ruler, T-shirt, baseball hat, circa 2000s (Box 80)
  - 2 Tachibana motorcycle helmets, circa 2000s (Box 72)
  - 2 Tachibana motorcycle helmets, circa 2000s (Box 78)
  - 2 Tachibana motorcycle helmets, circa 2000s (Box 82)
- Ephemera and realia, Series VII
  - John Holmstrom ephemera, fliers, news clippings, and ephemera (Box 83)
  - John Holmstrom ephemera, posters (Box 84 (Oversize))
  - John Holmstrom ephemera, posters (Box 85 (Broadside))
  - Ticket stubs, movie, band, and album press kits, stickers, flyers, posters (Box 86)
  - Posters, booklets (Box 87 (Oversize))
  - Bullet in High Times envelope (Box 88)
    Restricted fragile material. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - News clippings (Box 89)
  - News clippings (Box 90 (Oversize))
  - Clippings of artwork by Holmstrom (Box 91)
  - Clippings of artwork by Holmstrom (Box 92 (Oversize))
  - Button and matchbook collection (Box 93)
  - Letterhead, fliers, and other ephemera (Box 94 (Oversize))
  - Artifacts from CBGB's: Brick, lampshades (Box 95)
  - Artifacts from CBGB's: Flier-covered section of wall from CBGB's (Box 96 (Oversize))
  - Cowboy boots worn by John Holmstrom on the 1978 Sex Pistols tour. (Box 97)
    Scope and Contents
    A note from John Holmstrom is on the sole of each boot.
  - Posters, circa 1970s (Box 98 (Broadside))
  - Posters, circa 1970s (Box 99 (Broadside))
  - Posters, circa 1990s-2000s (Box 100 (Broadside))
  - Punk banner, vinyl, approx. 70" x 20", 2000s (Box 101 (Roll))
  - Punk poster on poster board, 2000s (Box 102 (Broadside))
  - Two "Punk" posters on boards, 2000s (Box 103 (Broadside))
- Audiovisual materials, Series VIII
  Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - 38 33 1/3 RPM records: #, A-C, 1960s-1990s (Box 104 (Record album storage))
  - 35 33 1/3 RPM records: C-E, 1960s-1990s (Box 105 (Record album storage))
  - 35 33 1/3 RPM records: F-H, 1960s-1990s (Box 106 (Record album storage))
  - 2933 1/3 RPM records: H-N, 1960s-1990s (Box 107 (Record album storage))
  - 35 33 1/3 RPM records: O-R, 1960s-1990s (Box 108 (Record album storage))
  - 35 33 1/3 RPM records: R-Z, Misc., 1960s-1990s (Box 109 (Record album storage))
  - 7 33 1/3 RPM records: Misc., 1960s-1990s (Box 110 (Record album storage))
  - 66 45 RPM records: #, A-I, 1960s-1990s (Box 111 (Record album storage))
  - 60 45 RPM records: J-S, 1960s-1990s (Box 112 (Record album storage))
  - 54 45 RPM records: S-Z, Misc., 1960s-1990s (Box 113 (Record album storage))
  - 90 compact discs, 1990s-2000s (Box 114)
  - 90 compact discs, 1990s-2000s (Box 115)
  - 55 compact discs, 1990s-2000s (Box 116)
  - 60 audio cassettes, 1980s-2000s (Box 117)
  - Videocassettes, 1990s-2000s (Box 118)
    - MTV News segment, "Nerve" magazine, undated; GENMSS951_0001; 1; 00:04:01; The timecode runs through the whole video. (Box 118, Item barcode 39002093672344)
    - Iggy Pop, Live in Paris A L' Olympia, Part I of II, running time 56:59, transferred; GENMSS951_0002; 1; 01:00:00 (Box 118, Item barcode 39002093672351)
    - "Go Mental": John Holmstrom, running time 2:43, undated; GENMSS951_0003; 1; 00:04:15 (Box 118, Item barcode 39002093672369)
    - F# Sharp TV, The Pink Show and John Holmstrom, undated; GENMSS951_0004; 1; 00:29:42 (Box 118, Item barcode 39002093672377)
    - Joey Ramones 50th Birthday Party at Hammerstein Ballroom, NYC, 38:00 raw footage (tape 2), 2001-05; GENMSS951_0005; 1; 00:28:23 (Box 118, Item barcode 39002093672385)
    - Racist cartoons, undated; GENMSS951_0006; 1; This videotape is not digitized. (Box 118, Item barcode 39002093672393)
      List and description of the cartoons are included with the tape.
      1. Warner Bros. "Sunday Go to Meetin' Time" (negro skips church and pays the price)
      2. Warner Bros. "Confederate Honey" (early Elmer Fudd joins the Confederate army)
      3. Warner Bros. "All This & Rabbit Stew" (Bugs with black sterotype [?] of Elmer
      4. Warner Bros. "Bugs Bunny Nips the Nips" (classic anti-Japanese wartime)
      5. Warner Bros. "Russian Rhapsody" (Hitler and "Gremlins from the Kremlin") - B. Clampett